Finding aid for Media Resources Center (University of Michigan) Films and Videotapes, 1930s and 1948-1987
Bentley Historical Library
- Series AF - Archives Film
  - Cazzie Russell, 1965; [851831-AF-434]; (Footage of UM vs Minnesota basketball game features Cazzie Russell. Shots of team warming up and game action, UM wins 88-85. Good shots of crowd in Yost Field House. (Film has been cut up and spliced out of order.)Features: Cazzie Russell)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp, b/w, sil, 880
  - Monkey Smash, circa 1970; [851831-AF-435-a]; (Footage of UM laboratory equipment used in testing design and impact resistance of football helmets includes shots of the sled and track used to simulate impact and a variety of measurement and date recording devices.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp, col, sil, 800
  - Monkey Smash, circa 1970; [851831-AF-435-b]; (Additional footage of laboratory equipment used in testing design and impact resistance of football helmets.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp, col, sil, 560
  - Dr. Les Soper, Monkey Hypothermia Experiment, [851831-AF-436]; (Footage of laboratory experiment on effect of hypothermia on monkeys. Shots of Dr. Soper conducting psychological tests on monkey, performing surgery on monkey, and measuring impact of hypothermia on heart function and brain activity.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp, col, sil, 760
  - Student Government Council Election, 1966; [851831-AF-437]; (Footage of campaign and election of student government officers includes shots of banners on Diag, posters, candidates speaking, candidates in WCBN studio, students voting in the Fishbowl, ballot counting, and a victory celebration.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp, b/w, sil, 300
  - Ford Foundation Grant, circa 1967; [851831-AF-438]; (Film of a meeting, possibly Board of Regents and Ford Foundation officials, apparently regarding Ford Foundations contribution to the UM $55 million capital campaign.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, neg, b/w, sil, 110
  - Rose Bowl Parade, 1951; [851831-AF-439]; (Footage of floats and a few bands from the 1951 tournament of Roses Parade, including the University of Michigan float. This film was produced by Sportsreel Productions.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil, 450
  - Clean Air Car, circa 1970; [851831-AF-440]; (Footage of a UM student in a laboratory performing emissions test on a car.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil, 80
  - Robot, circa 1970; [851831-AF-441-a]; (A UM engineering professor demonstrates a model robot.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil, 20
  - Robot, circa 1970; [851831-AF-441-b]; (UM aeronautical engineering students are shown working on designs of a robot, professor demonstrates a model robot.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil, 70
  - President Fleming's Inauguration, 1967; [851831-AF-442]; (Footage of the Fleming family and friends at tea at the President's House, Fleming gives a tour of the house, inaugural banquet in Michigan Union(?), procession and ceremony in Hill Auditorium, Fleming's address. (Sound track for part of speech.)Features: Robben Fleming, UM-Pres.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp; neg, b/w; b/w, sil; sil; sot, 850; 850
  - Regents '60, 1961; [851831-AF-443-a]; (This film consist of short clips from a number of the archives films made in 1960, apparently as a compilation to demonstrate the type of work being done in the first year of the archives film program.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, b/w, sof, 700
  - Regents '60, 1961; [851831-AF-443-b]; (Continues brief film clips from 1960 archives film.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, b/w, so, 700
  - NCAA Regional Tournament, 1965, [851831-AF-444-a]; (Original game footage of UM vs. Vanderbilt basketball game in regional finals of NCAA basketball tournament.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos; pos, col; b/w, sil; sil, 100; 100
  - NCAA Basketball Tournament, 1965, [851831-AF-444-b]; (Original game footage of UM vs. Vanderbilt in regional finals of 1965 NCAA basketball tournament. Includes some footage of post-game celebration and UM's regional championship trophy.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil, 300
  - NCAA Basketball Tournament, 1965, [851831-AF-444-c]; (Footage taken at 1965 NCAA regional baseball tournament, includes brief clip from UM vs. Dayton game but is mostly non-game footage including shots of the pep band, press table, and crowd.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil, 80
  - Rose Bowl Half-time, circa 1965; [851831-AF-445]; (Footage of UM Marching Band performing at half-time of Rose Bowl game.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp, col, sil, 120
  - Marching Band Travels, circa 1965; [851831-AF-446]; (Footage of the UM Marching Band in California preparing for performances in Rose Parade and at Rose Bowl game.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp, col, sil, 750
  - Rose Bowl 1965, [851831-AF-447-a]; (Footage of the last quarter of the UM vs. Oregon State Rose Bowl game and post game activities, including Marching Band plying on field, tearing down of the goal posts, and fan's celebration.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp, col, sil, 560
  - Rose Bowl 1965, [851831-AF-447-b]; (Game footage of Michigan vs Oregon State Rose Bowl.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil, 150
  - Rose Bowl 1965, [851831-AF-447-c]; (UM Marching band performance at half-time of Rose Bowl game. Features: Marching Band)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp; pos, col; col, sil; sil, 65; 120
  - Rose Bowl 1965, [851831-AF-447-d]; (Rose Bowl game footage including several Michigan scoring plays from the second-half and the final plays of the game, the UM Marching Band performing on the field after the game, and fans celebrating and tearing down the goalposts. Features: Marching Band)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil, 450
  - Ford Foundation Picture Sequence, [851831-AF-448]; (Film footage of photographs depicting natural resources, agricultural activities, industrial plants in Detroit, Grand Rapids and Battle Creek, and recreational and educational resources of Michigan. (Several takes, includes music but no narrative.))
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, b/w, sof
  - Reconstructive Ear Surgery, [851831-AF-449]; (UM doctor illustrates technique of molding an artificial ear which will be attached to a child suffering from an ear deformity.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp, col, sil, 55
  - Flu Vaccine, [851831-AF-450]; (UM researchers are shown preparing flu vaccine in a laboratory, injecting eggs with a virus.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp, col, sil, 95
  - Rose Bowl Parade, 1948, [851831-AF-451]; (Footage of the 1948 Tournament of Roses Parade including the UM Marching Band and the Michigan float. (Work print and original B-wind.)Features: Marching Band)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp; pos, col; col, sil; sil, 120; 120
  - Alumni Film, [851831-AF-452-a]; (Camp Michigania.; Footage of facilities and activities at UM Alumni Association's Camp Michigania, including shots of archery range, lakefront and beach, sailboats, cabins and dining facilities, and a UM professor lecturing.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil, 500
  - Alumni Film, [851831-AF-452-b]; (Continues footage of Camp Michigania activities including horseback riding and swimming. Also filmed footage of still photographs including a man jumping over the Diag "M", Vulcans at anvil, and Economics Building. (Filmed for "We Came to Ann Arbor"))
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil, 550
  - Campus Scenes, [851831-AF-453]; (Footage of a variety of campus and town scenes including "Shakey Jake" Woods playing guitar on the Diag, Ulrich's Bookstore, Overbeck's Bookstore, and campus buildings including Economics, LS&A, Kelsey, Engineering Arch, Hill Aud. and Dental School. Features: "Shakey Jake" Woods)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp; pos, col; col, sil; sil, 480; 480
  - Galens Collection and Christmas Party, [851831-AF-454-a]; (Christmas party for child patients at University Hospital sponsored by the Galens Society. Also footage of what appears to be a computer screen in which a man uses light pen to give instructions for plotting regression analysis?)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp, b/w, sil, 790
  - Galens Collection and Christmas Party, [851831-AF-454-b]; (Footage of Galens Society members collecting donations on campus and downtown Ann Arbor.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, b/w, sil, 575
  - Tom Harmon, [851831-AF-455]; (Three to five minute tape of UM football game in which a fan raced out of the stands and attempted to tackle Tom Harmon. (On two-inch videotape, apparently transferred from film. Tape #583. Also transferred to videocassette)Features: Tom Harmon)
    - Original:, 2-inch video
  - Michigan-California Football Game, 1940, [851831-AF-456]; (Ca. 5-10 minute tape of UM's 1940 season opening victory over California. (Two-inch videotape apparently transferred from film. tape #584. Also transferred to videocassette.))
    - Original:, 2-inch video
  - Michigan Stadium Dedication, 1927, [851831-AF-457]; (Ca. five minute clip from the dedication of Michigan Stadium in 1927. (Two-inch videotape apparently transferred from film. Tape #585.))
    - Original:, 2-inch video
  - Beaumont Memorial Dedication, 1954; [851831-AF-458-a]; (Footage of dedication ceremonies at the Beaumont Memorial on Mackinac Island commemorating Dr. William Beaumont, pioneer Michigan surgeon, includes series of speeches and shots of the Memorial building, former trading post of the Astor Fur Company.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, b/w, sil, 310, 00:08:40
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 5)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF458-a.flv
  - Beaumont Memorial Dedication, 1954; [851831-AF-458-b]; (Footage of dedication speeches and Memorial Building)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, b/w, sil, 460, 00:12:45
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 5)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF458-b.flv
  - Beaumont Memorial Dedication, 1954; [851831-AF-458-c]; (Continues footage of Beaumont Memorial building and crowd at dedication ceremony.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, b/w, sil, 433, 00:11:57
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 5)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF458-c.flv
  - Beaumont Memorial Dedication, 1954; [851831-AF-458-d]; (Continues footage of dedication ceremony.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, b/w, sil, 397, 00:11:07
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 5)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF458-d.flv
  - Beaumont Memorial Dedication, 1954; [851831-AF-458-e]; (Continues footage of dedication ceremony.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, b/w, sil, 392, 00:10:56
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 5)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF458-e.flv
  - Michigan-Duke Basketball Game, [851831-AF-459]; (Partial game footage from the UM vs Duke football game.)
    - Original:, 16mm film
  - Football Team Photo Day, circa 1970; [851831-AF-460]; (Film footage of the UM football squad posing for the official team photo. Features: Glen "Bo" Schembechler, UM-Ath.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp; wp, col; col, sil; sil, 219; 219
  - Dr. Hazel Losh's Heart Attack, [851831-AF-461]; (Footage of UM astronomy professor and number one football fan Hazel Losh suffering a heart attack on sidelines during a UM football game. Features: Hazel Losh, UM-Astron.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, sil
  - Fall Colors on Diag, [851831-AF-462]; (Footage of fall foliage on the Diag and other parts of campus, also pan shots of Palmer field and the hill dormitories, and students walking about campus.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp; pos, col; col, sil; sil, 230; 300
  - Aerial Shots of Campus, [851831-AF-463]; (Footage shot from the Goodyear blimp includes good views of the Law Quad, Central Campus, the Medical Campus, downtown Ann Arbor, and Michigan Stadium - empty and full.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp; pos, col; col, sil; sil, 1000; 1000
  - Alumni Film, [851831-AF-464-a]; (Aerial views of campus including good shots of North Campus and an empty Michigan Stadium. Also brief footage of UM-Dearborn and UM-Flint campuses.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp, col, sil, 850
  - Alumni Film, 1977; [851831-AF-464-b]; (Footage of the UM Alumni Marching Band and the Marching Band performing at half-time of a football game, shots of the crowd in Michigan Stadium and a few football plays.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp, col, sil, 580
  - President Fleming's Resignation, 1977; [851831-AF-465]; (Footage of UM President Robben Fleming's resignation announcement. Features: Robben Fleming, UM-Pres.; Sally Fleming)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp; pos, col; col, sil; sil; sot, 410; 450; 450
  - Amaizin' Blues, 1977; [851831-AF-466-a]; (UM choral group performs a number of "Michigan" songs. Features: Amaizin' Blues)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp; pos, col; col, sil; sil, 400; 400
  - Amaizin' Blues, 1977; [851831-AF-466-b]; (UM choral group performs a medley of Michigan songs. (Filmed for the Alumni Association film "We Came to Ann Arbor.")Features: Amaizin' Blues)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp; wp; pos, col; col; col, sil; sil; sil, 250; 150; 400
  - Alumni Film, 1977; [851831-AF-467-a]; (Film footage of still photos of early UM athletic teams, coaches and athletic events. (Filmed for the Alumni Association film "We Came to Ann Arbor.))
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp, col, sil, 640
  - Alumni Film, 1977; [851831-AF-467-b]; (Film footage of still photos of campus events and personalities from the early 1900s and of campus artifacts such as athletic programs, and dance posters.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp, col, sil, 900
  - Alumni Film, 1977; [851831-AF-468-a]; (Footage of interviews with UM alumni who have returned to campus for graduation, shots of various campus scenes, the Union, Ferry Field, graduates with their parents. (Filmed for Alumni Association film "We Came to Ann Arbor.))
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp; pos, col; col, sil; sil, 800; 800
  - Alumni Film, 1977; [851831-AF-468-b]; (Additional footage of interviews with alumni at various spots around campus.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp; pos, col; col, sil; sil, 300; 300
  - Football Crowds, 1977; [851831-AF-469]; (Close-up and pan shots of football fans in Michigan Stadium.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp; pos, col; col, sil; sil, 115; 115
  - Engineering Fund Raising, [851831-AF-470]; (Footage from the College of Engineering fund raising broadcast includes a variety of shots of campus particularly of Engineering Arch and North Campus engineering facilities, engineering labs, classrooms, and faculty. Pres. Fleming speaks from NC. Features: Robben Fleming, UM-Pres.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil, 630
  - Profs Copywork, [851831-AF-471]; (Film footage of still photographs of many UM professors, campus scenes, fraternity houses, and campus social events. (Apparently for the Alumni Association film "We Came to Ann Arbor," most photos are b/w.))
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp, col, sil
  - Campus Buildings, [851831-AF-472]; (Footage of several campus buildings including an Art School studio, a chemistry lab, and a Dental School lab. Also shot of Prof. Robert Angell standing in front of Angell Hall and of a theatre class rehearsing.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp; pos, col; col, sil; sil, 183; 190
  - Carillon Bells, circa 1976; [851831-AF-473]; (Film of the arrival from England of the new set of bells for the Baird Carillon, shows the bells being picked up at the Detroit harbor, transported to Ann Arbor and installed in Burton Tower.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp; col, sil, 400
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, b/w, sil, 00:11:51
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 5)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF473.flv
  - Student Relations, Student Housing, 1969; [851831-AF-473-a]; (Footage showing a variety of student housing: university married student apartments, single dwellings, apartments, a fraternity house (Dental School Fraternity,) sorority house, student dorms.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil, 100
  - Michigan Union 50th Anniversary, 1954; [851831-AF-474]; (Film of dedication of new addition to Michigan Union on the occasion of the 50th anniversary of the Union's founding, footage of Union activities and facilities including the swimming pool, bowling alley, study areas, main desk, and sleeping rooms.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, b/w, sil, 299, 00:08:22
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 5)
    - Streaming File:
  - Men's Gymnastics, [851831-AF-475]; (Footage of UM mens gymnastics team in competition at Crisler Arena. (1970s?))
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil, 750
  - Regents 1, circa 1961; [851831-AF-476]; (A filmed tour of the TVC studios with explanations of equipment, facilities, and the working of the studio. Apparently produced for presentation to the UM Board of Regents to demonstrate the work of the TVC.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, neg, b/w, sof; sot, 500; 500
  - Regents 2, circa 1961; [851831-AF-477]; (Short clips from a number of University of Michigan Television Center programs broadcast in the previous several years. Apparently compiled for presentation to the UM Board of Regent's.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, neg, b/w, sof; sot, 500; 500
  - Peace Corps 20th Anniversary, 1980; [851831-AF-478-a]; (Footage of a ceremony held on the steps of the Michigan Union marking the 20th anniversary of Pres. Kennedy's announcement of his plan for the Peace Corps.)
    - Peace Corps 20th Anniversary, 1980; [851831-AF-478-a]; (Footage of a ceremony held on the steps of the Michigan Union marking the 20th anniversary of Pres. Kennedy's announcement of his plan for the Peace Corps. Includes remarks by former director Sargent Shriver, Edmund Muskie, Sam Brown and others. Features: Harold Shapiro UM-Pres.; Richard Celeste)
      - Original: [missing]
    - Peace Corps 20th Anniversary, 1980; [851831-AF-478-b]; (Continues coverage of ceremony marking 20th anniversary of the Peace Corps. Includes remarks by Sargent Shriver, Richard Celeste, and Yolanda King. Features: Sargent Shriver; Richard Celeste; Yolanda King; G. Mennen Williams)
      - Original:, u-matic, pos, color, sound, 14:30
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 5)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-AF478-b.flv
    - Peace Corps 20th Anniversary, 1980; [851831-AF-478-c]; (Continues coverage of ceremony marking 20th anniversary of the Peace Corps. Includes remarks by Sargent Shriver, Richard Celeste, and current director Sam Brown. Features: Sargent Shriver; Richard Celeste; Sam Brown)
      - Original:, u-matic, pos, color, sound, 00:16:44
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 5)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-AF478-c.flv
    - Peace Corps 20th Anniversary, 1980; [851831-AF-478-d]; (Continues coverage of ceremony marking 20th anniversary of the Peace Corps. Includes remarks by UM regent Sarah Power and Sec. of State Edmund Muskie. Features: Sarah Power, UM-Regent; Edmund Muskie)
      - Original:, u-matic, pos, color, sound, 00:14:48
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 5)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-AF478-d.flv
    - Peace Corps 20th Anniversary, 1980; [851831-AF-478-e]; (Continues coverage of ceremony marking 20th anniversary of the Peace Corps. Includes conclusion of Sec. of State Edmund Muskie's remarks and an exchange with protesters, and Pres. Shapiro's closing statement. Features: Edmund Muskie; Harold Shapiro, UM-Pres.)
      - Original:, u-matic, pos, color, sound, 00:10:02
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 5)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-AF478-e.flv
  - Maggie Kuhn / Ralph Nader Interview on Co-ops, 1979; [851831-AF-479-a]; (Maggie Kuhn, leader of the "Grey Panthers" and an advocate of the cooperative movement discusses the philosophy of cooperative living and economic institutions and the cooperative movement's relation to consumerism and other social movements. Features: Maggie Kuhn)
    - Original:, u-matic, pos, color, sound, 22:13
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 5)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF479-A.flv
  - Maggie Kuhn / Ralph Nader Interview on Co-ops, 1979; [851831-AF-479-b]; (Conclusion of Kuhn interview and interview with consumer advocate Ralph Nader on the role of consumer and other cooperative organizations. Features: Maggie Huhn; Ralph Nader)
    - Original:, u-matic, pos, color, sound, 15:50
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 5)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF479-B.flv
  - Shapiro Inauguration, 1979; [851831-AF-480-a]; (Footage of the inaugural ceremony of UM President Harold Shapiro. Includes procession into Hill Aud., introduction of regents and former presidents, remarks by Hanna Gray, Irving Shain, and representatives of UM faculty, students and alumni. Features: Hanna Gray; Irving Shain; Richard Cochran, UM-Med.)
    - Original:, u-matic, col, sound, 00:55:00
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 5)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF480-A.flv
  - Shapiro Inauguration, 1980; [851831-AF-480-b]; (This tape of the inauguration of UM Pres. Harold Shapiro duplicates #480a but also includes the remarks of Saul Hymans of the UM Economics Dept. Features: Saul Hymans, UM-Econ.)
    - Original:, u-matic, col, sound, 00:51:43
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 5)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF480-B.flv
  - Fleming Dinner, 1979
    - Fleming Dinner, 1979; [851831-AF-481-a]; (Footage of a farewell banquet for UM former president Robben Fleming and Sally Fleming, includes remarks by UM regents Sarah Power and Dean Baker and former Chrysler president Lynn Townsend. Features: Robben Fleming, UM-Pres.; Sarah Power, UM-Regent; Dean Baker, UM-Regent; Lynn Townsend)
      - Original:, u-matic, color, sound, 00:16:49
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 5)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-AF481-A.flv
    - Fleming Dinner, 1979; [851831-AF-481-b]; (Continues footage of a farewell banquet for former UM Pres. Robben Fleming and Sally Fleming, includes remarks by UM regent Sarah Power, Robben Fleming, and Sally Fleming. Features: Sarah Power, UM-Regent; Robben Fleming, UM-Pres.; Sally Fleming)
      - Original:, u-matic, color, sound, 00:10:18
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 5)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-AF481-B.flv
    - Fleming Dinner, 1979; [851831-AF-481-c]; (Continues footage of farewell banquet for former UM president robben Fleming and Sally Fleming, includes remarks by Robben Fleming. Features: Robben Fleming, UM-Pres.)
      - Original:, u-matic tape, [unable to digitize]
  - Regents' Meeting / Shapiro Appointment, 1979; [851831-AF-482-a]; (Footage of special regents' meeting to announce the appointment of Harold Shapiro as new UM president. Regent Nederlander discusses the selection process and other regents comment. (Most of the time camera is on Shapiro while regents speak.)Features: Robert Nederlander, UM-Regent; Harold Shapiro, UM-Pres., Allan Smith, UM-Law)
    - Original:, u-matic, [unable to digitize]
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 5)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF482-A.flv
  - Regents' Meeting / Shapiro Appointment, 1979; [851831-AF-482-b]; (Continues coverage of a special regents' meeting announcing appointment of Harold Shapiro as new UM president. Includes comments by interim president Allan Smith and Shapiro. Features: Allan Smith, UM-Law; Harold Shapiro, UM-Pres.)
    - Original:, u-matic, color, sound, 00:12:44
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 5)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF482-B.flv
  - Regents' Meeting / Shapiro Appointment, 1979; [851831-AF-482-c]; (Continues coverage of a special regents' meeting announcing appointment of Harold Shapiro as new UM president. Includes a statement by Shapiro, introduction of Shapiro's family, and a brief interview with Shapiro. Features: Harold Shapiro, UM-Pres.)
    - Original:, u-matic, color, sound, 00:15:01
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 5)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF482-C.flv
  - Flint Humanities Conference, [851831-AF-483-a]
    - Flint Humanities Conference, [851831-AF-483-a]; (Footage of a Conference on Work and Leisure in Flint sponsored by UM-Flint and the Michigan Council for the Humanities. Includes opening remarks and talk by Al Rightly, former UAW official.)
      - Original:, u-matic tape, color, sof, 60:00